Let's head home for dinner
Mhm
In my previous life
when Fu Chenzhou reclaimed his place
I wasn't by his side
In this life
he wasn't forced back to the Fu family by the storm
he took my hand
and walked back
What are you looking at
Those who mocked me for marrying a bodyguard
are now praising my good taste
They changed their tune quickly
Mr Fu's identity was just confirmed
and you sound so composed
Not because of my status
It's because their
opinions never mattered anyway
Several partners in Nancheng requested a visit
Lu Group, Shengyuan Bank and
Gu Group
Gu Chengze finally lost his cool
Put Gu Group's visit request on hold
Go through formal procedures for project issues
No private meetings
Understood